<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on zyanchew</title>
    <link>https://zyanchew.github.io/portfolio/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on zyanchew</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 17:49:36 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zyanchew.github.io/portfolio/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Master&#39;s Graduation Project</title>
      <link>https://zyanchew.github.io/portfolio/projects/master_thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 17:49:36 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zyanchew.github.io/portfolio/projects/master_thesis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;📍Title: Synthesizing Social Networks for Travel Behavior Models&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This research explores the use of &lt;em&gt;Bayesian Belief Networks (BBNs)&lt;/em&gt; to synthesize social networks and it&amp;rsquo;s strength for further integration into travel behavior models. The study focuses on understanding how socio-demographic factors and social relationships influence joint activity participation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;💡 Key Findings&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Individuals with larger networks of friends are more likely to engage in activities such as dining out.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Those with more siblings in their networks tend to take family vacations more often.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;People are more likely to visit or host friends compared to colleagues.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These findings highlight the importance of both the size and the nature of social relationships in shaping mobility behavior.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human Mobility Challenge 2023</title>
      <link>https://zyanchew.github.io/portfolio/projects/mobility_challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 16:44:52 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zyanchew.github.io/portfolio/projects/mobility_challenge/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;📍 Human Mobility Prediction Challenge 2023&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The challenge involved using a synthetic human mobility dataset to train a deep learning model for predicting future mobility trajectories. The tasks are divided into two scenarios, business-as-usual and under emergency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;💡 Reflections&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Participating in the Human Mobility Predictions Challenge 2023 was a valuable learning experience.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;It allowed me to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enhance my coding skills, particularly in Python and machine learning frameworks.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Apply machine learning techniques to predict mobility trajectories in different scenarios.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Deepen my understanding of neural network mechanisms and explore their theoretical underpinnings.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;📈 Results&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bachelor&#39;s Graduation Project</title>
      <link>https://zyanchew.github.io/portfolio/projects/undergraduate_thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 13:33:43 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zyanchew.github.io/portfolio/projects/undergraduate_thesis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;📍Title: Dynamic Accessibility Measurement Using Human Mobility Big Data&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This project was conducted as part of my bachelor&amp;rsquo;s graduation thesis, focusing on analyzing human mobility data to evaluate accessibility changes during extreme events. By examining mobility patterns before, during, and after a hurricane, this study aims to reveal community resilience and recovery trends.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;📌 Key Takeaway&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;This study demonstrates how mobility data and data-driven approaches can offer valuable insights into infrastructure resilience and inform disaster preparedness strategies.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
